
var mockProblemSets = [ 
    {
        "id" : 100,
        "name" : "Scientific Notation",
        "level" : 1,
        "sequence" : 1,             
        "problems" : [
            {
                "questionId" : 1,
                "question" : "6.72 xx 10^3",
                "answers" : ["6720","672.02","672000","672"],
                "correct" : "6720",
                "correctIndex" : 0
            },

            {
                "questionId" : 2,
                "question" : "6.072 xx 10^3",
                "answers" : ["6720","6072000","72","6072"],
                "correct" : "6072",
                "correctIndex" : 3
            },
            
            {
                "questionId" : 3,
                "question" : ".600072 xx 10^3",
                "answers" : [".672","600.072","672",".60072"],
                "correct" : "600.072",
                "correctIndex" : 1
            },

            {
                "questionId" : 4,
                "question" : "672 xx 10^0",
                "answers" : [".72","672","72","720"],
                "correct" : "672",
                "correctIndex" : 1
            },
            
            {
                "questionId" : 5,
                "question" : ".00652 xx 10^3",
                "answers" : ["256",".065","6.52","6.052"],
                "correct" : "6.52",
                "correctIndex" : 2
            }
        ]
    },
    
    {
        "id" : 101,
        "name" : "Scientific Notation",
        "level" : 1,
        "sequence" : 2,             
        "problems" : [
            {
                "questionId" : 1,
                "question" : ".72 xx 10^5",
                "answers" : ["72000","72.02",".00672","672"],
                "correct" : "672000"
            },

            {
                "questionId" : 2,
                "question" : ".072 xx 10^5",
                "answers" : ["720","072000","7200","7.2"],
                "correct" : "72"
            },
            
            {
                "questionId" : 3,
                "question" : ".00072 xx 10^5",
                "answers" : [".72",".072000","72",".0072"],
                "correct" : "72"
            },

            {
                "questionId" : 4,
                "question" : ".0072 xx 10^3",
                "answers" : [".72",".072","72",".0072"],
                "correct" : ".072"
            },
            
            {
                "questionId" : 5,
                "question" : ".00652 xx 10^5",
                "answers" : [".652","652",".652","6.52"],
                "correct" : "652"
            }
        ]
    },

    {
        "id" : 102,
        "name" : "Scientific Notation",
        "level" : 1,
        "sequence" : 3,             
        "problems" : [
            {
                "questionId" : 1,
                "question" : "601.01 xx 10^1",
                "answers" : ["601.01","601.01",".60101","6010.1"],
                "correct" : "6010.1"
            },

            {
                "questionId" : 2,
                "question" : "60101 xx 10^9",
                "answers" : ["6010100000","60101000000000","60101000000000000",".000601010"],
                "correct" : "60101000000000"
            },
            
            {
                "questionId" : 3,
                "question" : ".00060101 xx 10^2",
                "answers" : ["601.01",".0601",".060101",".0000060101"],
                "correct" : ".060101"
            },

            {
                "questionId" : 4,
                "question" : ".0072 xx 10^3",
                "answers" : [".72",".072","72",".0072"],
                "correct" : ".072"
            },
            
            {
                "questionId" : 5,
                "question" : ".00652 xx 10^5",
                "answers" : [".652","652",".652","6.52"],
                "correct" : "652"
            }
        ]
    },

]


